Subtitle by:
aripp
Oh, yes.
You got donuts.
I already ate all the Boston cream.
Kyle?
This place gives me the creeps.
Relax.
That popsicle hasn't moved in 50 years.
Someone's hacking the system.
What?
The containment tank is destabilizing.
He's waking up.
We need more guys.
That is all the guys.
I thought we were going tubing.
Hold on, hold on.
Is this a race?
You're going down.
It is my destiny to claim the throne of
family champion, Hedgehog.
Haha, cute.
Are you sure you want to challenge the
fastest creature in the universe?
I mean, that's kind of my whole brand.
Okay, Tom and Maddie, count us down.
Right.
Don't worry, little sibling, right?
We're really healthy.
Me and my brothers used to do this kind of
thing all the time.
Tom, your brothers are lunatics,
and neither of them were born with the
power to trigger a global cataclysmic
event.
That's a fair point.
You hear that, boys?
No cataclysmic events, okay?
Let's keep this cataclysmic list.
Understood, Lord of the Donuts.
Then on your marks, get set, go!
And away out in front, to the surprise of
absolutely no one, it's the blue blur,
the red shoe rocket, the one,
the only... Come on, Sonic!
Good job!
Yeah!
Wait, in the what now?
I am also defeating you, Hedgehog.
Seriously?
Alright, you know what?
Time to light the afterburners.
It's a bird!
It's a plane!
It's Air Hedgehog!
Lost?
How is that even possible?
I do not lose!
I am also defeating you, Hedgehog.
Okay, okay, I get it, man.
I don't need to rub it in.
Come on, Sonic!
Catch up!
Yeah!
Wait, what's going on?
Why are you guys acting like... holograms?
Which means I remain the undefeated speed
champion of all time!
Yes!
And the crowd goes wild!
But also, what's going on?
Surprise!
Wait a second, you guys, what is all this?
Happy Be-Arthur Day?
Oh, it's Happy Be-Earth Day.
Today is the anniversary of the day you
came to Earth, bud.
It's your Earth Day birthday.
So the race was just a distraction, which
I totally didn't fall for, by the way.
Good try, though.
So you could throw a party for me?
Today we honor you, Hedgehog.
If it wasn't for you, none of us would be
here right now.
You boys are right, bud.
You know, the day you came to this planet
is the day all our lives changed forever.
And we became a family.
You guys, I don't know what to say.
Except... Let's party!
It's now on till the break of dawn!
Thanks for the surprise party.
It really means a lot to me.
Yeah, you deserve it, pal.
No way!
Is that... What?
Dude, can you just for once walk at my
speed?
Whoa.
Sonic.
This is your... Yep.
My old cave.
Oh, man.
I can't believe this is where you lived
all those years.
Hey!
My state-of-the-art security system!
Still works.
Hey, bud.
What's this?
Wow.
You know, I drew that on my first night on
Earth.
I wanted to remember where I came from.
I still miss her.
You think Longclaw would be proud of me?
I know she would, pal.
Because even though
you lost her at such a young
age, you didn't let your
pain change who you are.
In here.
Yeah.
In my lungs.
Or your heart.
Heart, right.
Yeah, makes more sense.
Not lungs.
Heart.
That's the thing about life, Sonic.
It's all about the choices we make.
You're gonna make some good ones, and
knowing you, you're gonna make some bad ones.
But...
As long as you remember
to listen to your heart, you're
gonna make the right choice
when it matters the most.
Thanks.
I don't know what I'd do without you.
I'd probably be a totally different
hedgehog.
2024?
I've been trapped for fifty years?
Why won't you leave me alone?
Take him down!
I have dishonored my marshmallow.
It's really just a question of temperature
and distance.
It's not a competition.
This is so nice.
Peace.
Quiet.
Finally.
What did we
do?
Or what did they do?
What did you do?
I don't know.
I do a lot of stuff.
Mr. and Mrs. Zulkowski?
Aliens.
Aliens?
Excuse me?
Is that like we're from different planet?
Oh, yeah, we are.
I guess we are aliens.
Please continue.
I'm Director Rockwell.
There is a very dangerous situation
unfolding right now in Tokyo.
Commander Walters is requesting Team
Sonic's immediate assistance.
Team Sonic?
Who picked that name?
Love it.
Ten out of ten.
No notes.
Tom and Matty, put the s'mores on ice.
Because Team Sonic is off to save the day.
We're back.
Good evening and welcome to Tails Air
Flight 1012.
We're looking at an on-time arrival into
Tokyo.
Okay, Captain.
We got a rogue alien on the loose.
How do we find him?
Start with the giant fireball?
I love it.
Let's start with the giant fireball.
Finally, some action.
Okay.
Time to gear up.
Titanium handcuffs.
Completely indestructible.
I don't need your silly gizmos,
Fox.
And you know why?
Because I am one million percent muscle.
Yes, good.
You've been listening.
We're over the drop, sir.
All right, here we go.
Showtime.
Now look, we don't know if it's Godzilla
or Hello Kitty down there, but as long as
we stick together, there is nothing we
can't handle.
Team Sonic on three.
One, two, three.
Team Sonic!
Talk about low-budget flights.
No food or movies?
We're out of here.
What happened here?
Looks like Gun got their butts kicked.
Keep your eyes open.
Tails, anything?
Whoa, these energy readings are off the
charts.
Look out!
One million percent.
Are you guys seeing this?
He looks just like you.
Impossible.
You're a colorful bunch.
Um, excuse me.
Why do you look like me?
I don't look like you.
You look like me.
Why do you look like me?
Hey, you know what?
I'll ask the questions, new hedgehog.
Who are you?
Why do you look like me?
This is a waste of time.
Walk away before you get hurt.
Whoa, whoa, easy, buddy.
We don't want to fight you.
Actually, Sonic, I would like to fight.
Not now.
Why don't you stop throwing cars at us for
a second and come down here to talk?
You jumped out of a gun helicopter.
There's nothing to talk about.
All right, then.
Enough!
Knuckles, no!
Let us talk without fists!
Knuckles!
Knuckles, Knuckles, are you okay?
No, not really.
Who is this guy?
He is much more impressive than the
hedgehog I fought previously.
Dude, I'm standing right here.
Now come on, you can't take us all at
once.
Okay,
he took us all at once.
Weakling.
Don't try to follow me.
Sonic, I know that look.
Going after him is a bad idea.
When has that ever stopped me?
I gotta ask, wanna hedgehog to another?
Who does your highlights?
Hey, dangerously weaving through traffic
is my thing.
Coming through!
Why are you running away?
We were just getting started.
The more you talk, the harder I wanna hit
you.
Watch out!
I'm gonna throw up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
1.21 gigawatts.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Sonic, are you okay?
I'm fine, guys.
And before you ask, I
handcuff myself for tactical
reasons that I do not
have time to explain.
You shouldn't have gone off on your own.
We're supposed to be a team.
Sorry, buddy.
I'm still working on this teamwork thing.
So now what?
Well, I'm not jumping out of any more
helicopters until we get some answers from Gun.
We need somewhere to regroup.
I know just the place.
One, two, three.
Whoa!
It's an ambush.
You'll never take us alive, foul beast.
Calm down, Knuckles.
This is a chow garden, one of the top 10
must-see spots in all of Tokyo.
It's a perfect place for us to blend in.
Are you Detective Pikachu?
Yes, he is.
He does look like a Pokemon.
Pika pika.
Commander Walters.
Sonic, thank God you're all okay.
I'm sure you have questions.
Just a big ticked off red and black one?
Who was that guy?
Shadow's story began a lot like your
Sonic.
But where you found
family and friends on
this planet, Shadow
found only pain and loss.
It begins over 50 years ago with a meteor
crash in a quiet corner of Oklahoma.
The meteorite contained a life form.
The ultimate life form.
Shadow's power, his chaos energy,
went far beyond any living creature.
The scientists who
discovered and believed this
power would usher in
a new era for humanity.
But Shadow's power proved too dangerous.
A terrible accident destroyed the lab,
taking human lives with it.
The project leader was blamed for the
incident and imprisoned.
With the program cancelled, Shadow was a
loose end no one knew how to deal with.
Too dangerous to be walking free,
too valuable to destroy.
So I had him placed into stasis.
Indefinitely.
Wait a second, if Shadow's been on ice for
50 years, someone had to help him escape.
True, but there's only a few people in the
world who even know of Shadow's existence.
Egg Drones?
But Robotnik is supposed to be dead.
Konnichiwa?
I'm sorry, we already had our big
motorcycle chase for the evening?
Commander Walters!
Commander Walters, are you okay?
Sonic, take this.
What is it?
A key to the most powerful weapon Gunt has
ever built.
You're the only one I trust to keep it
safe.
Commander Walters.
Medevac is on route.
This launch key is missing.
I knew they couldn't be trusted.
Why are we running from Gunt?
Aren't we on the same team?
Until we get more information,
we're not trusting anyone.
Follow me.
Hold it right there, Tokyo Drift.
Who are you?
It's the goat milker!
Relax.
I'm not here to fight.
Then why are you here?
And why did you free Shadow?
Are you kidding?
The last thing we want is more super
-powered hedgehogs running around.
The doctor had nothing to do with it.
And I can prove it.
Please.
Join me in the crowd.
And now back to the last mission.
I have fallen in love with another.
But who, Gabriela?
Tell me.
My twin brother, Pablo?
Bastard!
Buenos dias.
Hermano!
Let that be a lesson to you, Juan.
Family is a field of emotional claymores
that leave you abandoned, betrayed...
and weeping while you eat cake,
which creates copious amounts of adipose
tissue and what some calloused individuals
refer to as...
man boobs.
We have visitors.
Really?
I thought I was having an anthropomorphic
nightmare.
We're the only person I could trust in the
world showing up with all my worst enemies
while I was in a bathroom, playing congas
on my big fat belly.
Sorry, sir.
I don't believe it.
Eggman's alive.
And he's never looked worse.
Well, maybe this is what not giving a damn
what you think I look like looks like.
Sir, right now we have an even bigger
problem.
Oh, come on.
There's an imposter out there using your
technology.
Imposter?
That's impassa-what?
No, my sweet mechanized spawn.
Whomever this party-pooping
posse is looking for has
stolen my persona and the
precious babies from my egg sack.
Well, I'll soon egg-sacked my revenge.
You see what I did there?
It's time for the dramatic soap opera
twist where this pablo reveals his won.
I cross-referencing the ciced coordinates
of each girl's energy spikes.
I can track my babies to the imposter's
base of operations right about there.
Sonic, I hate to say it, but I think we're
both after the same person.
Hold on, hold on.
You're not suggesting we team up with Dr.
Robot Stink, are you?
Perhaps the fox is right.
It could be our only chance to find this
mysterious, more impressive hedgehog.
Ugh.
All right, Egghead.
I hate to say it, but it looks like we're
partners.
On one condition.
Dude, you have serious issues.
What?
Where are you?
Do this!
Tinker Taylor, I need room.
Think Elvis circa 1976.
Sir, I don't have the proper materials.
Found some.
Resourceful.
Hey!
This is a restricted area.
That's okay.
She's the professor's granddaughter.
He takes her everywhere.
Welcome to the lab, Maria.
I'm Captain Walters.
Oh, do you know where my room is?
Yeah, down the hall and to the right.
Make yourself at home.
But, um, let's lose the skates.
Okay, kiddo?
Okay.
Let's go.
Whoa!
Look at all those stars.
They're like diamonds.
My grandfather says it can take hundreds
of years for the light of a star to reach
Earth, and by the time we see it,
the star might not even exist anymore.
Isn't that crazy?
A light shines even though the star is
gone.
Yeah, it does.
I wonder which one you came from,
Shadow.
I don't know.
I don't know anything about my home.
This is your home, Shadow.
Earth.
Maria, do you think I'm dangerous?
What are you talking about?
The way the scientists look at me,
I can tell they're afraid.
Like I'm the horrible thing from that
movie we watched.
I don't know what I am.
You're my friend, and you can do or be
anything you want.
Not because of your powers, but because of
who you are in here.
I don't know what I'd do without you.
I knew my father was the one that killed
one of the bad guys.
I worked as a branding expert,
always in my team.
I was in the competition for one of his
battles.
One of them was a sniper and I've never
truly known who he was before.
So good luck to him.
Professor, it's good to see you,
Shadow.
I knew you'd come home.
I can't get her out of my head.
The pain.
It's too much.
And that is why we have to punish them.
Okay, I don't like you and you don't like
me.
Let's get this over with quickly.
Out of my way, dorkupine.
Dorkupine?
Really clever.
This door is six inch thick solid steel on
a pressurized latch.
I'll need a moment to
calculate the molecular
density and invert
the venting mechanics.
I unlocked him.
Subtle as always.
Fist for brains.
Easy, Shadow.
Those are the guests I've been expecting.
Let's give them a warm welcome.
What is this place?
Looks like a military base, but nobody's
been here for years.
I wonder if it's haunted.
Haunted?
Nobody said anything about being haunted.
What's the matter?
You afraid of ghosts?
Nothing scares an echidna warrior.
Uh, yeah.
Do you remember what happened last movie
night?
There's no such thing as a friendly ghost.
So, which way do we go?
I know.
We should split up.
Everyone with hideous, brightly colored
fur take the left and the middle.
Stone and I will go right.
No, no, no, no.
I'm not letting you out of my sight.
Tails, you and Stone go left.
Knuckles, you take the middle.
Eggman, you and me go right.
By all means.
We could use some time together to work on
your trust issues.
You know what?
You're right.
I should be more trusting.
I mean, you've only tried to kill me
twice.
Just a dark, creepy hallway.
Nothing to be afraid of.
You hear that, ghosts?
You don't frighten me.
Get a grip.
I'm just gonna come right out and say
this.
You're adorable.
Thanks.
So, what's it like being Sonic's
assistant?
Do you have a daily routine?
Paid time off?
Benefits?
Oh, I'm not Sonic's assistant.
We're teammates.
He's the leader, Knuckles is the muscle,
and I'm the gadget guy.
We all have a role to play.
That's what makes the team so special.
That and the fact we're best friends.
You are?
Well, yeah, just like you and Eggman,
right?
Of course, yes.
Me and the doctor.
Best of friends.
It's definitely what we are.
Wow.
Look at all this stuff.
This was more than just a military base or
lab.
It was a home.
People lived here.
He had a family.
Is that what I smell?
The stench of domestic harmony?
You ever wonder what your life would have
been like if you had a family?
Hmm, no.
Maybe you wouldn't have gone full
supervillain.
I have no parents, no aunts, no uncles.
And something about my attitude renders
me...
...undesirable to all possible genders.
My future is a cul-de-sac.
The robot nickname ends...
...avec moi.
Yes, I know French.
Is this where you grew up, Shadow?
No wonder you're so mad.
This place could really use a beanbag
chair and some comic books.
What happened here?
I'm tired of giving you warnings.
Where'd you go, hedgehog?
I wasn't finished trauma-dumping.
My darlings.
My eggy-weggings.
Memories... ...lie the
corners of my mind.
Misty watercolor memories...
...of the way...
...we were.
Don't believe it, don't you?
It's impossible.
Is it?
It couldn't be.
Are you?
Imposter!
You stole my babies.
They know who their real daddy is.
Drone-napper?
Magnificent creations, my boy.
I borrowed them to lure you here and
reunite our family.
Is he I owe?
I'm your grandfather, Gerald Robotnik.
My grandfather?
But how?
And why?
And who did what with whom?
You hail from an ancestry of excellence.
Tied directly a moi.
Yes, I know French.
You do look like me, but fatter and older.
And there's that funny smell.
But the resemblance is uncanny.
It's as if we're two characters in a movie
being played by the same actor.
But I need real proof!
Ivo, we have very little time.
But I could field a couple of queries.
Name the most elegant formula in
mathematics.
Euler's identity.
E to the i times pi plus one equals zilch.
European capitals arranged alphabetically
by the fourth letter.
Riga, Monaco, Sarajevo, Tirana.
The speed of light divided
by the speed of sound
divided by the speed of
the bus and the movie speed.
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
17,893.33333.
Rounding up.
17,894 mph.
And for all the marbles.
Good.
I lost mine.
A rare lung disease.
And the longest word in the English
dictionary.
In numinal ultra microscopic silico
-volcano-choleosis.
Pop, pop.
In the saggy flesh.
But looking pretty good for a hundred and
ten.
Oh, Grampy-poo.
Where have you been my entire life?
Wait.
Where have you been?
My entire life!
Locked in a top-secret prison for the last
50 years.
Made it kind of hard to send Christmas
cards.
Now, you're probably wondering why I
brought you here.
You didn't bring me here.
I used my unparalleled intellect to track
you down.
Heard the plan I concocted with my
unparalleled intellect.
You'll see.
I have the answer to everything.
Come on, kiddo.
I don't know.
Someone tell me this is some kind of
concussion-induced nightmare?
There's two Eggmen now?
Double your villains, double your fun.
Two robotniks are way worse than one.
Chest bump?
No.
Stone, why are you tied up?
Do that on your own time, you sicken me.
You must be the long-lost grandson.
And you must be another stinking hedgehog.
So you're the one behind all this?
The shadow breakout?
The attack on Walters?
That musty old man smell?
How dare you insult me with your
unsolicited exposition?
Shadow, get the key.
Where is it?
Ha!
Good one, Hot Topic.
Do you really think we'd be that stupid?
To bring the key right to you?
Yep, we're that stupid.
Gun took everything from us.
And now we are going to take everything
from them.
With this, my masterpiece of malevolence.
The Eclipse Cannon.
In exchange for my
freedom, I gave Gun the
most powerful weapon
mankind has ever seen.
Capable of delivering a precision strike
anywhere on Earth.
Our first target, Gun Headquarters.
But firing a weapon that powerful could
threaten millions of innocent lives.
Yeah, Terra bite me.
This is one of two keys required to launch
the Eclipse Cannon.
The other is locked inside Gun
Headquarters.
Once we have both, I will take rightful
control of my weapon.
I'm in.
Holy crap!
Spacious and crustaceous.
Thank you so much for inspiring this
little adventure.
It really worked out for me.
And you wonder why I have trust issues.
Shadow, wait.
Don't do this.
I know you're hurting, but don't let that
change who you are inside.
I've spent 50 years reliving what they did
to her.
This is who I am inside.
Nice magic marble.
Real scary.
That actually is real scary.
It's a mini black hole.
It's going to suck in all the matter in
this base.
Fear not, friends.
Even my teeth are muscles.
Sonic,
try to reach one of my rings.
Got one.
Check this out.
Trickshot.
Come on.
Come on!
Call Google Maps.
I've spent years trying to cleanse the
cosmos of that spiny blue speed freak.
And you did it.
In one afternoon.
There's nothing we can't destroy.
Together, my boy.
Charting route to gun headquarters in
London, sirs.
ETA four hours.
As the crap flies.
By all accounts, we're ahead of schedule.
We should take this time to get to know
each other better.
Wow.
What?
You mean spend some qua-qua-qua?
All at any time?
You've read it for this your whole life.
How would you choose to spend one perfect
day with your new grand-pal?
Live without him.
But let's talk about him.
And done.
Masterpiece.
Look at that.
Yay!
It's really been great having time to
ourselves.
Right.
Absolutely.
I just feel so relaxed, you know?
Clear-headed.
Look at all these new interests we've
found.
So many hobbies.
So many.
After the action and adventure of the last
few years, I could get used to this.
Same.
Tom and Maddy, we need your help
on a super... Knuckles, do you mind?
Oh, excuse me.
Tom and Maddy, we need your help on a
super dangerous top secret mission.
Thank God.
Let's go.
Yeah, we're in.
Really?
You're in?
Just like that?
Yes.
It was getting so boring without you guys
here.
No offense.
Boring.
No, none taken.
I mean, whatever crazy plan you're cooking
up, the answer's yes.
Great, but first things first,
what is that?
Oh, this is...
Little Tom.
Isn't he great?
I told you to get rid of that.
It's very creepy.
That's all I'm gonna get rid of you.
Okay, that's crossing a line.
You are in so much trouble.
Okay, this is it.
The belly of the beast.
Gun headquarters in London.
Tom, we're finally gonna get to see London
together.
Hey, I told you we'd get there someday,
baby.
Okay, so here's the plan.
I run in super fast.
Fly over that water, no problem.
Then right when
I get to the... Ah!
What just happened?
Congratulations.
You just got incinerated by their energy
shield.
We'll need to shut it down by planting a
USB drive in their server room.
That will give me full control over it.
That's what we need you two for.
Couple badass spies, that's what we are.
Mr. and Mrs. Smith.
Once we disable the shield, you'll face
the laser hall.
These high density bad boys will cut you
into tiny pieces.
And cut those pieces into even tinier
pieces.
Once again, can't we just get Tom Cruise
to do this?
Nope, because not even he could break into
the vault.
Why is it empty in there?
Because we have no idea what's on the
other side of that door.
To prevent the vault from ever being
accessed by a ring, all images and
schematics have been wiped from Gunn's
database.
So for the last leg of this heist...
We're going in blind.
Okay, I'm just gonna say it.
It sounds like this plan will work a heck
of a lot better if Sonic used the Master
Emerald to go golden god mode to get the
key.
No way, Maddy.
The Master Emerald is too powerful to ever
use again.
We made a promise to each other to keep it
hidden.
In a location only Knuckles knows.
As guardian of the Master
Emerald, anyone who tries to
take it away for any reason
will become a sworn enemy.
Okay, sheesh.
No need to get all growly on me,
buddy.
You guys are always telling us to make
good choices.
Well, this is the right choice.
Okay, I guess we're going to...
When Casey died in London, when I got Bad
Man ready to shut it down.
Bad Man ready to shut it down.
London, baby!
Gunn headquarters is right there.
Let me go in, get the key, and destroy
anyone in my way.
I want revenge.
Patient Shadow, just let us handle this.
And I promise you'll have revenge on a
scale you couldn't possibly imagine.
Come on, Grand Daddio.
We've got dirt to do.
Suits.
Right here, sir.
Stone, babysit the hedgehog.
Keep the crab on a low boil.
It's time for more family bonding.
Come on, Shadow.
Got fresh avocados in the crab.
We'll make guac.
Revenge guac.
Guys, are you ready for me yet?
I've been waiting here all day.
Sonic, we literally just started.
Tom, Maddie, are you in position and
ready?
We were born ready.
Let's do this.
Knuckles, how about you?
I have taken my perch atop the giant
clock.
Now, where is this glass I'm supposed to
break?
Actually, Knucks, your job is to break
glass in case of emergency.
Understood.
I will shatter this glass like the jaw of
a vile foal.
In case of emergency.
I will plow arising like the skull of a
loathsome bridal.
Just to be clear, the emergency is the
important part.
The glass will beg for mercy under the
shadow of my mighty fist.
Guys, remember, we're a team.
Now let's focus.
Please.
You know what?
Let's move on.
All right, everyone knows what to do.
Tom and Maddie, you guys plant the USB
drive.
I'll disable the traps.
Sonic will snag the lunch key.
And Knuckles, you stand by to...
Break glass in case of emergency.
See?
He gets it.
Then we're all set.
Hologram time.
You go first.
Tom, it's me, Rachel.
Can you believe it?
We're both in London together.
Have you met your sister?
Try again.
Unless you're not up for this mission.
Yeah, maybe you want to be back in Green
Hills baking sourdough and...
Thomas Michael Wachowski?
Yeah.
You brought aliens to
my wedding, punched
out my husband and
buried me in an avalanche.
Your day of reckoning is at hand.
Yeah, that's perfect.
Okay, now for her better half.
My name is Randall, and I am too much to
handle.
Welcome to the gun show.
Baby, would you describe me as jacked,
juiced, or shredded?
I would describe your head as swollen.
Let's get to work.
Agent Randall, handle.
I'm here to have lunch with my lovely
wife, Rachel.
I'm sorry, Agent Randall.
This facility is currently locked down.
Command level clearance only.
One minute.
Tails, we have a problem here.
They must have tightened security after
Shadow's escape.
I got this.
You must be new here.
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Rachel.
Rachel gonna get you fired.
Do you know what gun stands for?
Of course, Guardian Unit.
Getting ultra nasty.
Do you want me to get ultra nasty?
Nasty nasty?
No, ma'am.
Okay, then.
Then go ahead and take those little sad
fingers and start tippity-tack-tack-tack.
Mm-hmm.
That's right.
Go on.
Sorry for the inconvenience, ma'am.
Mm-hmm.
That's what I thought.
My God, I love being Rachel.
Did it work?
Yeah.
Ow!
Director Rockwell, seeking access to the
server room.
Just one moment, ma'am.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, it's her.
It's her.
It's the real her.
What do we do?
Okay, did it work?
What's going on?
What am I doing wrong?
Ow!
Aye, aye, captain.
Who are you, Popeye?
I panicked.
I was joking.
Jeez!
Get it together.
Okay, Tails.
What are we looking for?
Security servers in the seventh row.
Twenty-third cabinet.
Are you guys finished yet?
This is taking forever.
Uh-oh.
Has the time come to break the glass?
Or at least break something?
All right, hang tight, guys.
Maddy's about to insert the drive.
Ready?
Three, two, one, go.
It didn't work.
Did you put it in the right way?
Try punching it.
Do not try punching it.
Oh, take it out and blow on it.
Yes!
Oh, come on, Tom.
There's absolutely no sign of the big
evidence to support.
Never mind, it worked.
A little trick from the 90s.
I mean, best decade ever, right?
I'm shutting down the outside sensors now.
Yes.
Hold on, is there supposed to be another
USB drive here?
One with a giant mustache on it?
Oh, no.
I've got two heat signatures en route to
the vault, which can only mean...
Our robotics have entered the chat.
Wait.
Puppy seat?
Grand geezer.
Donde esta?
I'm right here.
If you weren't family, I could have got
you like a pheasant.
I mean... Try to keep up.
And now back to la oritima passion.
Oritima passion can only belong to one.
No.
It can only belong to one.
Gabriella, she killed them both.
She's not a prize to be won.
Kill this, murder that...
You need to lighten up, Shadow.
We're about to rule the world.
When we're done, there won't be anything
left to rule.
That is dark, even for you.
What are you and the professor up to?
Hello, what's this?
I knew I saw an outside signal.
Cheerio, I guess someone forgot to flush.
What now, my cunning cohort?
Just a little teamwork.
Hey.
The lasers... don't seem
to be penetrating my suit.
They're conforming to the shape of my
bodacious bard.
Of course.
I designed these suits to create a field
of laser-bending thermal distortion.
Wasn't sure it would work till now.
You're a heartless son, rotten to the
core.
I'm... So now we can
just dance right through.
That sounds like a challenge.
Caught him right up.
Don't hold back.
Cause you woke up in the morning with the
initiative to move so I'll make it harder.
Don't hold back.
If you think about it, so many people do
be cool and look smarter.
Don't hold back.
And you shouldn't even care about the
those in the air and the crooked stairs.
Don't hold back.
Cause there's a party over here so you may
as well be here with the people care.
Don't hold back.
The world is out of date.
The time has come to... galvanize.
Come on, come on, come on.
My finger is on the button.
Push the button.
The robotics are almost at the vault.
We're out of time.
I'm going.
No, Sonic.
I haven't disabled the trap yet.
Too late.
Look at me.
I'm running on the wrong side of the road.
Well, I've got to take in the sights.
Paul, John, George, the other one.
Loud American coming through.
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Hello, Ga-Ga.
We quit Hogwarts?
Hear ye, hear ye.
Sonic the Hedgehog wants a cup of tea.
Hold this for me, please.
You're not going to make it.
I can make it.
I'm going to make it.
I'm not going to make it.
Made it.
Excuse me.
Coming through.
No time for autographs.
Gotta go.
Bye.
Our destiny awaits.
Stop right there, robo scum.
Let's do this.
Coming.
Too slow, Eggman.
Now, if you don't mind, I've got to get
that key.
Whoa.
My feet.
Why can't I use my beautiful feet?
Because this vault is armed with variable
gravity.
No kidding.
Green goes up and red takes you down hard.
Rockwell, listen to me.
The Robotniks are planning to...
Oh, they're planning on stealing the
second key just like you are?
Yes, I'm aware.
I called it.
The second Commander Walters was attacked.
So, thank you for taking the bait and
falling right into my trap.
I don't believe this.
I know, grandson.
A woman in the military.
Let's go.
Robotnik.
You're calling full spandex, huh?
Who's the fossil?
That's my grandfather, you dough-eating
dimbutsill.
Who's there?
A couple of bleeding hearts here to rescue
their emotional support animals.
Enough.
It's over.
The only way you're leaving here is in
handcuffs.
There is no other way out.
You know, there might be one other way
out.
And what is that supposed to mean?
Hey, big guy.
I think it's time to...
Break class in case of emergency!
Nothing can stop Team Knuckles.
Open fire!
Knuckles, turn the stuff off!
Hurry!
On it!
Uh-oh.
Ha!
See how you like...
Can you move?
No, not at all.
Tails, can you?
No!
I'm stuck!
We might be here a while.
Where's the key?
Whoa!
What was that?
We might have a problem.
I'm moving!
Well, go get it, grandson!
Hey!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
No, no, no!
I'm almost there!
Sonic!
That was so not worth it!
You okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Sonic!
Hey.
Sonic one, concrete boulder zero.
Thanks for the save.
Getting a little close, don't you think?
Secure the room!
She's got the key.
I got an idea.
Commander Walters.
Sir, you're... Still alive?
I'll die before I let that key fall into
the wrong hands.
Thanks for keeping it safe.
I'll take it from here.
That's an order, Director Rockwell.
Now, organize the reinforcements.
Yes, sir.
Guys, guys, I got the key.
I repeat, I got the key.
Now, let's get out of here.
Commander Walters.
No, no, no, wait!
What?
Tom, everyone's clear!
Come on, let's go!
You, what are you...
Tom!
Tom, Tom, what happened?
Speak to me, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, it's gonna be
okay.
Please, please, please, get up.
Come on, please, wake up.
Wake up, wake up, wake up, come on!
Wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Maria...
What did you do?
What I had to.
Oh, my God, Tom!
Help me up, Tim!
Freeze!
Come on!
Any tricks up your sleeve, Captain
Burntastic?
We got what we came for.
Great job, Shadow.
We have both keys.
So where's your little science project?
It's closer than you think, my boy.
Welcome to my masterpiece.
I must hand it to Gunn.
They built her to my exact specifications.
It's... remarkable.
Astounding.
Yes.
That's my genius, Gran Gino.
And I have one more surprise.
It's a new suit!
What?
I'm a chip off the old block.
I'm a chip off the old block!
What do you want, Stone?
I'm busy.
Doctor, I have a bad feeling about this.
I don't think your grandfather's been
completely honest with us.
It was something Shadow said.
There's more to their plan.
How dare you!
You've been jealous of my long-lost
grandpop, Tartt, since the very beginning.
I no longer require your obsequious
groveling.
Consider this your notice of termination.
Your letter of reference will be ill for
loser.
Of course, I'll expect you to stay on
until you've been successfully cloned.
But you and I are done!
Like a blackened catfish dinner!
Sir, it's too dangerous and I'm not there
to protect you.
I already lost you once!
Unsubscribed, blocked and reported.
I can't lose you again.
Do the honors, grandson.
Here we go.
It'll be okay, Sonic.
It'll be okay?
Tom is fighting for his life and you think
it'll be okay?
The fox is simply trying to comfort you.
Comfort's not what I need right now.
I need to stop them.
By any means necessary.
Wait, you don't mean...
The Master Emerald.
The Emerald must never be wielded for
vengeance.
Not ever.
We swore that it would be okay.
Don't talk to me about Oats.
Not now.
But you told Tom using the Emerald wasn't
the right choice.
Well, now it's the only choice.
And if neither of you have the guts to
help me, then I'll do it alone.
But I thought the three of us were a team.
I thought that's what made us special.
I'm not asking you twice, Knuckles.
Where is the Master Emerald?
Your heart is being consumed by anger,
Hedgehog.
You are in no condition to make decisions
right now.
I know you're upset about Tom.
We all are.
Last chance.
Where is it?
Don't do this.
Part of our oath is to trust each other.
And I must abide by that promise,
even if you have chosen to break it.
But heed this warning.
The Master Emerald is guarded by a
fearsome warrior and to seize this
ultimate power, you will have to go
through him.
Okay, Wade.
All comes down to this.
Last few seconds.
Whipple down the ice.
He shoots!
He scores!
Wayne Whipple is a champion again!
Oh, hey, Sonic.
You see my goal?
Pretty sick, right?
I'm here for the Emerald.
Look, Sonic, I'm sorry.
I promised to guard this Emerald with my
life.
I will do whatever it takes.
Well, I tried.
This is an urgent national emergency
broadcast.
A spacecraft designed by
the Agency Gun has been
hijacked and launched
out of the River Thames.
All residents are urged to seek immediate
shelter.
Professor, is this really what Maria would
have wanted?
The question isn't what Maria would have
wanted.
It's what do they deserve?
Remember what she meant to us.
Remember what they took from us.
Kids!
We have to go, now!
They want to take Shadow away from us,
Maria!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Those are children!
We've got our orders on us!
Stand down!
Maria!
Excuse me, Grand Pasadoble.
What is that thermal nuclear journal
doing?
Infusing the core with Chaos energy.
That's my little secret.
The Eclipse Cannon is about to turn this
planet into a flaming pile of rubble,
wiping out everything.
And a 25,000 mile radius.
Including us.
What?!
We can't annihilate the Earth?
By combining our genius, we can rule
humanity.
Together!
Humanity is a failed experiment.
If anyone should know that, it's you.
All your life you've been rejected by this
world.
You have nothing down there.
No one who cares about you.
But I have you now.
We're family.
We have each other.
Oh, Ivo.
You're no Maria.
The moment I lost her, my family was gone
forever.
The only way to give
Maria's life meaning is
to destroy the world
that took her from me.
So I'm burning it all down!
It's done.
Good work, Shadow.
I'm prepping the firing sequence.
The weapon will be fully charged in 10
minutes.
It's almost finished, Maria.
You will have justice.
What is that?
His gun launching missiles at us?
Impossible.
It's moving too fast.
It's him.
This ends now!
Now you know my anger.
The pain I've felt for 50 years.
And you've made the same choice I did.
I'm nothing like you!
We'll see.
Show yourself, coward!
You were right about one thing.
This ends now.
What's happening?
Where are they?
Up there.
Where?
Higher.
Left yourself open.
What are you doing?
Porting your evil plan!
Not the mustache!
Green!
Let go of three.
One, two, three!
Oh, a narrow fist.
I haven't seen that since I hate-watched
Green Lantern in 2011.
I was saving it for Comic-Con.
But now there won't be a Comic-Con!
Where are your friends?
They tried to stop you, didn't they?
But you came anyway.
Your anger was too much.
What kind of hero abandons his friends to
pursue revenge?
Abandons his family?
Don't you dare talk about my family!
And here I thought you cared for them.
Especially the one...
What's his name?
Tom?
No!
Go ahead!
Finish it!
What are you waiting for?
Do it!
I'm right here!
You didn't let your pain change who you
are.
In here.
This is not who I am.
What are you doing?
You won!
Take your revenge!
There are no winners with revenge.
Look at all those stars.
They're like diamonds.
The last time I sat beneath stars like
this...
I was with her.
I've felt this pain for so long.
It's all I know.
When I lost Longclaw, I felt the same way.
Did your pain eventually go away?
No.
But in time, I learned there's something
even more powerful than pain.
The love we felt for each other.
That's what you need to hold on to,
Shadow.
Maria might be gone, but your love will
always remain.
The light shines, even though the star is
gone.
This whole mess is my fault.
I've been so blinded by rage, I thought I
had no choice.
You always have a choice.
Making the right one is never easy.
One more thing I learned
is that when you really
screw something up,
you can't fix it on your own.
Gotta go fast.
Don't tell me you've got a catchphrase.
That's right, new hedgehog.
And everyone loves it.
With that love, if you fail or if you
borrow With that love, you may never find
your way Oh yeah I will not try to stop my
elders from destroying the world.
Playtime is over.
There's no going back now.
Set.
Up.
Defense.
Damn you, autocorrect!
Mantis!
Neat.
I'm right here, arachnid.
That's what I call mantis-scaping.
That's elder abuse.
Shadow, I see you've chosen betrayal.
And you were once so useful to me.
Ready to recycle some tin cans?
Just trying to keep up.
Please, Grancy.
Don't do this.
Sorry, kiddo.
Bring your grandkid to work day is over.
Any last words?
Just one thing that I never thought I'd
say.
What is it?
I love you.
No.
It was something even better.
But I'm not going to say it if that's the
way you're going to be.
Okay, bye.
Grandchildren.
All the fun and none of the
responsibility.
Who said life was pointless?
Oh, right.
You did.
Victory!
See what you want about my granddad?
He made one hell of a bug zapper.
You've got to stop that laser.
I knew there was something I was
forgetting.
We're out of time.
The cannon is about to fire.
Where are you?
Oh, you know, just making friends.
They're all yours.
Follow me.
Now this might hurt a little.
So this was your plan?
Would someone mind shutting down the giant
death ray?
We can't stop the cannon from firing.
But we can steer it away from the Earth.
Coming around the starboard.
Aye, aye, doc.
Here we go.
It's a little tight.
Definitely not power steering.
Keep turning.
Jump in any time here, guys.
Oh, much longer.
Yes!
I did it!
Look what you did!
Hey, look down there!
Sonic!
Knuckles, please tell me you have a...
Last one.
Let's make it count.
Ready for a little face of fall?
Deep breath.
One, two, three!
Really?
What's happening?
The reactor core is overloading.
It's only a matter of time before it
blows.
So what does that mean for Earth?
A radioactive atmosphere?
Rain that kills the crops and melts your
flesh?
Other than that...
We're not done here.
You try to stabilize the reactor.
Buy me some time.
I'll push the station away from Earth
before it explodes.
Folks, this is our last chance.
To do the right thing.
Let's do this.
Core integrity failing.
I got you, Sonic!
Let's do this.
Initializing reactor core stabilizers.
This is Dr. Ivo Robotnik.
Dedicating my final live stream...
to one very special henchman.
Agent Stone.
No, no.
Doctor, wait!
If I can't rule the world...
I might as well save it!
You're the one and only person who ever
cared about me.
Don't do this, Doctor, please!
Stone... You're the one and only
person who ever cared about me.
You were more than a sick of it to me.
You were...
a sick of friend.
I'll miss your lattes with steamed
Austrian goat milk.
I love the way you make them.
I guess there's only one thing left to
say.
Hm?
It's been a real drag!
Thanks for nothing.
Sonic, look!
Shadow and Robotnik.
They sacrificed themselves...
to save everyone.
You always have a choice.
Guys, I'm really sorry for running off
like that.
I shouldn't have left you behind.
The truth is... you're the best
teammates a hedgehog could ever ask for.
And the best friends.
Can you ever forgive me?
Team Sonic?
How about just team?
Big finish!
Now that's what I call teamwork.
Okay, it's ready!
Knuckles, how could you?
Gotta be faster than that!
Give me a break.
I'm still moving a little slow over here.
Donut Lord!
Yay!
Ahh!
Okay, Knuckles.
I am having the love.
Get in here Ozzy.
It's great to be back together.
We're stronger than ever.
And nothing is gonna stand in our way.
Except...
that one piece of unfinished business.
And way out in front to the surprise
of absolutely no one... It's the blue blur.
Often imitated, never duplicated.
The one, the only...
Let's do this!
Alright boys, try and keep up.
Days like this don't get much better.
Top down good fam, good weather.
Days like this we don't miss never.
Yeah, yeah.
Last night things got a little bit crazy.
Pulled up doing about 180.
Life goes fast so there ain't no maybes.
Yeah, yeah.
Just give me that sunset.
Give me that ride.
Give me them stars out.
Four wheel drive.
Taking that back road.
Yeah, no lie.
Man, that sure feels nice.
Give me them real ones.
Ones I know.
Do a little two step do-si-do.
Turn it up loud.
Bringing that crowd.
Take it up high and drive it low.
We do this everywhere we go.
I think you know.
This ain't no white horse rodeo.
When we pull out the green lights I'll
show.
I think you know.
That we go running, running, running.
Until we run out of room.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
We do this everywhere we go.
I think you know.
This ain't no white horse rodeo.
When we pull out the green lights I'll
show.
I think you know.
That we go running, running, running.
Until we run out of room.
Oh yeah.
Running, running, running.
Until we run out of room.
Oh yeah.
Sonic the Hedgehog is family champion once
again.
Tails?
Knuckles?
Okay.
Yeah, I overshot the finish line.
Okay, so how do I get back?
Pro tip.
If you're going to take a shot at the
fastest creature in the universe,
you better not miss.
Um, I'm flattered by the cosplay,
but you got a few details wrong.
I can't blame you though.
It's hard to copy perfection.
That's a neat trick.
What?
Who are you?
Subtitle by:
aripp